thanks for hanging out with me so much
since Matt was seduced by the sirens
called the mediocre street artists no
problem but also I don't really have a
choice you keep showing up wherever I am
in talking to me about how you're mad
yeah I feel like your friendships really
blossoming to Lady gaga no you text me
I've had enough infatuation with this
guy is unreasonable nobody is that
interesting I'm gonna say something
don't do it you don't have the social
clout to face him Jake I see how it
works we all work side by side for years
and some fraud and a loser mash shows up
and suddenly is everyone's best friend
Greg I expect this from you but Fred
Laura I thought our friendship meant
something those are any of their names
face it you're just a ripoff artist and
you probably wear that mask cuz you have
an ugly face
[Music]
actually Jake I wear the mask because
when I was 22 a child molester pushed my
face into a campfire
another thing that doctors did you ever
make my face a face again it's not what
you wanted to hear Wow
Jake I think you should leave fine come
on grace we're not wanted here
right behind you Jake you are so brave I
know
[Music]